<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
 Copyright 2014 The Android Open Source Project

 Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 You may obtain a copy of the License at

     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="description_info">Info</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="toggle_turn_on">NN:On</string>
    <string name="toggle_turn_off">NN:Off</string>
    <string name="toggle">Use NNAPI</string>
    <string name="nothing">Please select a crop disease from the drop down above.</string>

    <!--barley diseases-->

    <string name="net_blotch">Net blotch is a common disease of barley, and is caused by the fungus Pyrenophora teres. It has two forms: the spot form (SFNB) and the net form (NFNB). 
Symptoms are most commonly found on leaves, but can occasionally be found on leaf sheaths. They develop as small circular or elliptical dark brown spots becoming surrounded by a chlorotic zone of varying width. 
The net form of net blotch starts as pinpoint brown lesions, which elongate and produce fine, dark brown streaks along and across the leaf blades, creating a distinctive net-like pattern. Older lesions continue to elongate along leaf veins, and often are surrounded by a yellow margin
Both SFNB and NFNB can be effectively controlled with an integrated strategy incorporating varietal selection, crop rotation, seed treatment and crop monitoring with a view to fungicide applications, if required.
A new seed treatment containing fluxapyroxad (Systiva®) is available for control of both net blotches in barley.</string>

    <string name="powdery_mildew">Powdery mildew (Blumeria graminis f.sp. hordei) is currently one of the most serious disease of barley in Australia. Especially in WA, growers have reported increasingly severe and epidemic levels of disease. These epidemics are due to the failure of both genetic and chemical control methods.
Reduce the proportion of area sown to barley varieties rated very susceptible (VS) or susceptible (S) to powdery mildew. Where possible utilise varieties with better resistance which may not require fungicides for powdery mildew management.
Control volunteer barley plants prior to seeding, particularly of S varieties, this will reduce inoculum of powdery mildew (and leaf rust) carried into the season.
Balance crop nutrition, particularly ensuring adequate potassium on deficient soils and avoid excess use of nitrogen fertiliser.
Use appropriate fungicides to manage disease threats present within the cropping system.</string>

    <!--cotton diseases-->

    <string name="asycochyta_blight">Ascochyta Blight forms lesions on cotyledons, leaves, stems, and bolls. Lesions on the cotyledons and leaves approach 2 mm (less than 0.1 in) in diameter, are white to light brown and circular in shape. Elongated can-kers on the stem are reddish-purple to black or ash gray in color. Small, black fruiting structures are likely to be embedded in symptomatic tissue.
Ascochyta Blight has been reported in most major cotton producing regions. Yield loss is rarely reported, but is possible under conditions such as prolonged cloudy weather with cooler temperatures and rainfall.
Use fungicide treated seed, avoid planting in cool wet weather, and incorporate cotton residue to encourage decomposition, which helps in fields with a history of Ascochyta Blight.</string>

    <string name="boll_rot">Boll Rot is known to be caused by several fungi and bacteria including Fusarium, Diplodia, and Alternaria species. These diseases infect the bracts and enter the boll at cracking or through injuries to the boll. Lesions appear that eventually spread turning the entire boll brown to black. 
With most diseases, environmental conditions are the biggest factors in infection rates. Persistent rain, moisture and/or cloudy weather with cooler temperatures are huge contributors to Boll Rot incidence – especially when occurring at boll cracking.
Boll feeding insects have the potential to pierce bolls and create an opening that allows infection of Boll Rot pathogens if present.
Management promoting a healthy plant and good fruiting through fertility and water management, maintaining appropriate plant populations and preventing rank growth can all help to reduce risk of pathogen incidence and infection. If you have no scout or consultant who is experienced with stink bug management then Bidrin is recommended to be sprayed during the 3rd-4th week of bloom, and again 2-3 weeks later. If fields are highly infested, are near purported over-wintering sites such as pine tree stands, or if there has been a mild winter which increases potential for stink bugs, then additional sprays or border sprays should be considered.  Again there is no single solution, and boll rot will continue to plague producers in Alabama. But there are some management options to consider to potentially reduce risk and severity.</string>

    <!--guava diseases--> 
    
    <string name="fruit_fly_damage">When ripe, guavas emit a pungent, musky odor that attracts fruit flies. Fruit flies lay their eggs beneath the fruit\'s skin, and the maggots feed on the flesh. The damage causes guavas to rot. Fruit fly infestations often spread quickly, but prompt treatment can get populations under control.
Adult fruit flies damage the fruit where they lay their eggs causing blemishes and discoloration. The maggots bore into the fruit, develop inside and pave the way for secondary invaders (fungi or bacteria), which cause extensive rotting and dropping of fruit. Damaged fruits are unfit for human consumption. Damage symptoms do not vary on different crops.
Always use pesticides in a lawful manner which is consistent with the product’s label. Failure to follow the label may result in crop injury, poor control or residue problems. Consult the list of registered pesticides for your country to determine which products are legally allowed for use. Certain pesticides are acknowledged to present particularly high levels of hazards to human health and/or the environment according to internationally accepted classification systems (see the Plantwise pesticide red list), and as a consequence their use is not advised.</string>

    <string name="guava_rust">The guava rust, caused by Puccinia psidii Wint., attacks all the young tissues of the plant and can cause losses up to 80 to 100%. With the objective of verifying the efficiency of some fungicides on such disease, an experiment was conducted in the agricultural year 1994/1995, in Louveira, State of Sao Paulo. The plants used were white Ogawa cultivars, with 4 years of age. The statistical outlining of blocks at random was used, with 6 treatments and 4 repetitions, with 3 plants per parcel of land. The fungicides used and their respective doses of active ingredient per 100 l of water were: chlorothalonil PM 75%-150g; chlorothalonil SC 508%- 150 g; mancozeb PM 80% - 160 g; mancozeb PM 80%-160g pand copper oxychloride PM 50% - 100g. The applications, in the number of 8, began in December 1994, using an average of 1 liter of fungicide mixture per plant. The evaluations were done in February and March 1995, collecting 60 fruit from the central plant, and giving grades from 0 to 5 in accordance with the affected area. The data were transformed in arc sine √chi/100. For the comparison of the averages it was used F and Tukey tests at 5%. All treatments were superior to the control. The products based on chlorothalonil were the most efficient in the control of guava rust, presenting a control above 85%.</string>

    <!--mustard diseases-->
    
    <string name="alternaria_blight">The fungus Alternaria cucumerina causes Alternaria leaf blight. This disease is most common melon, but can also affect cucumber, pumpkin and squash. Alternaria leaf blight does not commonly infect fruit. It can reduce yield and quality through reduced plant vigor and sunscald of exposed fruit.
It revealed from the investigation that the foliar spray with mancozeb at 45 DAS followed by hexaconazole at 60 DAS was found most effective in controlling Alternaria leaf and pod blight  severity and increased seed yield over untreated control. It may be tested as prophylactic sprays at farmers’ fields in mustard, so that a recommendation can be made for control of this pathogen.
Rotate vegetables so that a location goes three or more years without growing any member of the squash family. Use drip irrigation instead of overhead sprinklers if possible. Do not work in plants when wet. Remove and destroy infected plants at the end of the season in small gardens. In large fields, till under crop residue at the end of the season. Several fungicides are available for use against Alternaria leaf blight. Preventative sprays are effective but are only necessary in fields with a history of Alternaria leaf blight. Commercial growers should refer to the Midwest Vegetable Production Guide for specific fungicide recommendations.</string>

    <string name="white_rust">Also called Staghead or white blister, white rust disease affects cruciferous plants. These plants are all members of the cabbage family (Brassicaceae) and include such vegetables as broccoli, cauliflower, Brussels sprouts and kale and can ruin your crop. White rust is one of several species of the fungus Albugo. It commonly occurs when nights are cool and damp and days are warm. The perfect time for growing cruciferous vegetables also provides the perfect growing conditions for Albugo. Controlling white rust fungus would be easy if we could control those spring and fall temperatures since it flourishes between 57°F. and 68°F. (14° to 20°C.). Unfortunately, we can’t control temperature any more than we can control the spring rains or the dewy mornings this fungus adores.
If your garden has been plagued by white rust disease in the past, you should look for resistant strains in the future. There are no fungicides specific to white rust treatment and once the disease becomes rampant, there is little to be done. That being said, fungicides used to treat downy mildew are sometimes effective against white rust, particularly the more leafy crops. Treatment must begin at the first signs of infection. The methods for controlling white rust fungus or how to prevent white rust are largely organic.
The second step in controlling white rust fungus is crop rotation. Infected beds should not be replanted with cruciferous vegetables for at least three years.</string>

    <!--pumpkin diseases-->

    <string name="downy_mildew">The causal agent of downy mildew, Pseudoperonospora cubensis, is a plant pathogen in the water mold family, whose survival is only associated with living cucurbit tissue. Therefore, it does not survive the winter in the Midwest and must be re-introduced each year. On pumpkins and winter squash, the symptoms may resemble powdery mildew, causing yellow spotting that tends to brown out. As the lesions age, they usually become necrotic on all types of cucurbits and the leaves often senesce. This dieback is normally first noticed on the oldest leaves near the center of the plant. Regardless of the variability in appearance of the leaf lesions among the different cucurbits, the one similarity and diagnostic sign is the presence of purplish-gray sporangia on the bottom side of the leaf within the lesions. These are most readily observed when conditions are cool and moist, with or without the aid of a hand lens. They may also appear when an infected leaf is placed in a closed plastic bag with a damp paper towel for 12 to 24 hours. The leaves are the only portion of the plant directly affected by downy mildew, though the resulting loss in leaf surface can cause loss of yield, misshapen fruit and sunscald.
To fight downy mildew in pumpkins, select growing sites with good drainage and airflow, full sunlight and low humidity. Avoid overhead irrigation to prevent leaf wetness. Insure adequate, but not excessive fertility. Monitor the crop frequently – scouting is one of the most important things you can do to combat downy mildew economically.</string>

    <string name="southern_blight">The first symptom of the disease is a mid-day wilting of the plant. Leaves turn yellow and within a few days the plant collapses leading to plant death. The rapid collapse of the plant is due to girdling of the stem at the soil surface, and the entire root system is often completely rotted. The fungus develops a white mycelium, which may be fan shaped, over the surface of the stem. Light brown bodies (sclerotia) may be observed embedded within the white mycelium. These sclerotia turn dark brown with age. The fungus also infects fruit in contact with infested soil, developing sunken, yellow spots which decay and collapse. Large amounts of white mycelium and sclerotia can form on the fruit as it decays.
A good sanitation program is generally the most effective control measure. Remove and burn infected plants to prevent inoculum build-up. Deep plow crop residue to reduce inoculum levels. Rotate to non-host crops (corn and small grains) for a period of three to five years. Good water management can help reduce soil moisture, which in turn reduces the amount of germinating sclerotia in the soil. Fumigation can also provide control. Some fungicides have proved effective in controlling this disease.</string>

</resources>
